tarheeltimes.com 2018-07-25

# Privacy Policy - Tar Heel Times

The privacy of visitors to Tar Heel Times is extremely important to us. 

At Tar Heel Times, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. The following explains the types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Tar Heel Times, and how we safeguard your information. We never divulge or sell your personal information to third parties unless required to do so by law. 

**Log Files**   
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Time Warner Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you an advertisement once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on Tar Heel Times to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Raleigh real estate ads to someone in Raleigh, NC, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing sports-related ads to someone who frequents sports sites). 

We may also collect non-identifiable personal information such as Age, Gender, and Personal Interests to share with our advertisers in aggregate fashion so that they may provide more targeted advertisements to the site. 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums.
